ifitandhealthy.com 2013-09-22

# Privacy Policy » iFitandHealthy.com

**iFitandHealthy.com** takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.

## Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

We require that you enter your email address to post a comment. The reason for this is twofold: spam prevention and comments moderation, both of which are necessary to keep the comments on this site appropriate and spam-free.

_We never share your email address with anyone_.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, iFitandHealthy.com uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

## Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

## Contact Information

If you have questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please [**contact us**](http://ifitandhealthy.com/diet-fitness-contact/ "contact us") for further clarification.

[Credit: This privacy policy was generated using [Privacy Policy Plugin](http://www.synclastic.com/plugins/privacy-policy).]
